and welcome to another installment of
欢迎来到另一期
spring tips in this installment we're
在本期的 spring 技巧 中，我们
going to look at apache camel apache
要去看阿帕奇骆驼阿帕奇
camels and enterprise integration
骆驼与企业整合
framework from from apache of course on
框架从Apache当然
which a lot of developers from Red Hat
来自Red Hat的很多开发人员
work it has been around for a long time
工作已经存在了很长时间
it's been around for at least as long as
它已经存在了至少
for example spring innovation so this
例如春季创新，因此
technology has become rather entrenched
技术已经变得根深蒂固
a lot of people are using it and so
很多人正在使用它，所以
while I like spring innovation I do want
当我喜欢春季创新时
to explore the wonderful world of apache
探索apache的美好世界
camel and i want to particularly thank
骆驼，我要特别感谢
my friend Klaus absent who who spent
我的朋友克劳斯不在，谁花了
some time with me to sort of interest me
和我在一起一段时间让我感兴趣
up to all the latest and greatest stuff
直到所有最新和最伟大的东西
in in the support for camel for a spring
在支持骆驼的春天
boot now today we're gonna look at
今天启动，我们来看看
spring boot 1.5 which is just a little
spring boot 1.5这只是一点点
old that's actually you know we're now
旧的，实际上你知道我们现在
at 2.0 X for spring boot but there is
在 spring boot 的2.0 X下，但有
support for spring boot tornado in the
支持 spring boot 龙卷风
pipeline due in apache camel to 2.2
apache骆驼到2.2到期的管道
which i think is awesome
我认为很棒
right spring boot - he's purposely
正确的 spring boot -他是故意的
giving it to that - that - that's super
给它-那-超级好
cool so that's coming and as I
很酷，所以来了，就像我
understand it that's in the next month
了解下个月
or so but you know open source timelines
左右，但是您知道开源时间表
being what they are don't hold don't
作为他们不持有的东西不要
hold me to that they're very well maybe
让我坚信他们可能很好
maybe the reason for that to change
也许改变的原因
but anyway sooner rather than later and
但无论如何，宜早不宜迟，
in the meantime we can certainly use the
在此期间，我们当然可以使用
snapshot version if you like you can
快照版本（如果可以）
just add the the maven repository that
只需添加的Maven存储库
Apache has for for snapshots or in this
Apache具有用于快照或在此
case we can use the spring boot 1.125
情况下，我们可以使用 spring boot 1.125
series and just use Apache camel GA bits
系列，仅使用Apache骆驼GA位
with it right now so there has been
现在有了它，所以有
support for spring boot a very good
对 spring boot 的支持很好
support for spring boot in apache camel
支持apache骆驼的 spring boot
since camel 2.15 and this support has
自骆驼2.15以来，这种支持
gotten better and better and better to
变得越来越好
the point where now I can't believe I
现在我简直不敢相信我
haven't done a video on this stuff
还没做过关于这个东西的视频
before this is a really quite a whole
在这之前是一个非常完整的整体
embrace of the spring wood ecosystem and
春季木材生态系统的怀抱和
so we're gonna just walk through some of
所以我们将只走一些
the basics here and we'll look at some
这里的基础知识，我们将看一些
of them some of the things that you can
他们其中一些你可以
do with with apache camel and then
用阿帕奇骆驼做，然后
particularly how you can do them with
特别是你如何做
with spring and spring boot in
带有弹簧和 spring boot
particular and then we're gonna look at
特别的，然后我们来看看
what i think is arguably the most
我认为最有争议的是
important part of apache camel which it
阿帕奇骆驼的重要组成部分
which is this in maize
玉米是这个
catalog of connectors and I know
连接器的目录，我知道
integration framework is in some way
集成框架在某种程度上
very much about its the it's raft it's a
非常关于它的筏子
stable of connectivity of the things
物联网的稳定性
that with which it can integrate and
它可以与之整合的
here apache camel is no slouch and then
这里的阿帕奇骆驼没有懈怠，然后
of course finally we'll look at the look
当然，最后我们来看一下
at the world of patrick camel and how
在帕特里克骆驼的世界以及如何
that works with spring and particularly
适用于春季，尤其是
with some of the spring into eq eco
随着春天的发展
system that takes message channels right
正确处理消息通道的系统
including for example the likes of
包括例如
spring innovation spring cloud stream
春季创新 Spring Cloud Stream
springing cloud dataflow and the website
不断涌现的云数据流和网站
web service was re WebSocket support in
Web服务重新支持WebSocket
the spring game you see so a lot of good
春季游戏，您会看到很多好处
stuff here to look at today we're gonna
今天要看的东西
focus on all these different components
专注于所有这些不同的组成部分
right we're gonna look at all these
对，我们要看所有这些
different components what we're gonna
不同的组成部分
we're gonna focus on different
我们将专注于不同
components today there is a great list
今天的组件列表很棒
i'm just want to make sure we're we've
我只是想确保我们
called that out camel that apache at or
叫那只在或
look for such components that HTML and
寻找HTML和
we'll start our journey as usual here at
我们将照常从这里开始我们的旅程
the initializer so i'm gonna go ahead
初始化程序，所以我要继续
and build a new application but again
并建立一个新的应用程序
keep in mind we've got two dead o2 out
请记住，我们有两个死亡的氧气
there right now I could use it I could
现在我可以使用它了
use this but the the initializer
使用这个但是初始化
checkbox well disable itself because
复选框很好禁用自身，因为
there is no to that Ogier weenies
没有那个Ogier的肚子
candidate version of Apache camel and
候选版本的Apache骆驼和
it's coming right is coming soon enough
它马上就要来了
so and it you can even get this code to
这样，您甚至可以获取此代码以
work with today doe but for our purposes
与今天的美国能源部合作，但出于我们的目的
since it's almost identical the the code
因为代码几乎相同
footprint we're just can use one at five
我们只需要五分之一就可以使用
and we're gonna create an example here
我们将在这里创建一个例子
called camel and we use Apache camel now
叫做骆驼，我们现在使用Apache骆驼
we also want to use let's see we want to
我们也想使用让我们看看我们想
use ActiveMQ so we use a Jamis activemq
使用ActiveMQ，所以我们使用Jamis activemq
instance we'll use what else to run ease
实例，我们将使用其他方法简化运行
Lombok that can hurt spring integration
可能会损害弹簧整合的龙目岛
right well one needs this pre
好吧，一个需要这个前提
integration support we'll come back to
集成支持，我们将回到
that in just a bit
只是一点
and I think that ought to do now that'll
我认为现在应该这样做
give us the ability to do some basic
让我们有能力做一些基本的
stuff and again we'll look at what
东西，我们再来看一下
opportunities they are you know what
他们是你的机会，知道什么
they what opportunity lay out there for
他们有什么机会在那里
us to to further expand this example if
我们将进一步扩展这个例子
we get to that point but for now I think
我们到了这一点，但现在我想
this is a good start so we'll go ahead
这是一个好的开始，所以我们继续
and generate project
并生成项目
and when I open this up as usual in the
当我像往常一样在
IDE so here we are
IDE，所以我们在这里
CD downloads ueo camel dot zip and what
CD下载ueo骆驼点zip以及什么
we're gonna do is we'll just start with
我们要做的就是开始
the the simple thing that you can
你可以做的简单的事情
possibly do right so um let's see here
可能做对了，所以让我们看看这里
we go that's gonna start up and we're
我们去那会开始，我们
going to open up the property file went
要打开属性文件去了
to the build loads here so let's see
到这里的构建负载，让我们看看
all right so the application has loaded
好的，因此应用程序已加载
and now we can build an application that
现在我们可以构建一个应用程序
takes advantage of apache camel so a
利用了阿帕奇骆驼，所以
couple things to keep in mind here is
这里要记住的几件事是
that all we've done with the initializer
我们用初始化程序完成的一切
is load up the camel spring boot starter
正在加载骆驼弹簧启动启动器
which gives us a patch of camel to that
这给了我们骆驼的补丁
to that one to Judith to that one that
到朱迪思去那一个
one and this wart this certainly works
一个，这疣当然有效
this isn't a working version of Apache
这不是Apache的有效版本
camel but the the truth is this is
骆驼，但事实是，这是
probably not the best way to use Apache
可能不是使用Apache的最佳方法
camel you see apache camel has a huge
骆驼，你看到阿帕奇骆驼有一个巨大的
amazing
惊人
I mean blew me away stable of components
我的意思是炸毁了稳定的组件
so the first thing I like to do is to
所以我想做的第一件事是
change my build to use a dependency
更改我的构建以使用依赖项
management section so that I can import
管理部分，以便我可以导入
these these dependencies unqualified
这些依赖项不合格
right so that what in order for us to do
对，以便我们做什么
that we need to add a dependency
我们需要添加一个依赖项
dependency management section here like
依赖管理部分在这里像
so and we're gonna add a dependency
所以，我们要添加一个依赖项
management section that looks like you
看起来像您的管理部分
know anything else you've seen before
知道你以前见过的任何其他东西
for example of spring cloud so org
例如，Spring Cloud So org
apache camel oops sorry
apache camel oops对不起
the dependencies got ahead of myself
依赖已经超越了我自己
their dependency and we want to add the
他们的依赖关系，我们想添加
camel spring - but-- - dependencies
骆驼春天-但--依赖
support please be right i hope that's
支持请正确，我希望那是
right and that it looks right okay org
正确，看起来正确org
apache camel all right org apache camel
apache camel all right org apache camel
and the version will be camel dot
版本将是骆驼点
version and camel that version will
版本和该版本的骆驼
define up here camel dot version and the
在这里定义骆驼点版本和
camel dub version that we're gonna use
我们将使用的骆驼配音版本
is 2.2 1.1 right so that's that and this
是2.2 1.1对，就是这样
is a bomb of bill of materials vom
是物料清单炸弹的炸弹
import so we're gonna make it a import
导入，因此我们将使其导入
scoped palm type right there we are
掌心型，我们在那里
there's our are our dependencies there
这里是我们的依赖
we are and and that's it that's the
我们是，就是这样
that's i think that's it so we now we
我认为就是这样，所以我们现在我们
can first of all we can change this we
首先我们可以改变我们
can drop this from the the build there
可以从这里的构建中删除
we don't need it
我们不需要
I ended up coming automatically and now
我最终自动来了
we can bring in all the other stuff that
我们可以引入所有其他东西
we want to use right all the other
我们想用其他所有权利
interesting bits that we want to use so
我们想要使用的有趣的地方
let's today focus on a very simple
今天让我们关注一个非常简单的
example our first examples we'll look at
我们来看的第一个例子
J you know we'll look at the file system
J您知道我们将研究文件系统
and Jane s now JMS is the reason we're
和Jane的JMS现在是我们
using JMS is because we have a nice auto
使用JMS是因为我们有一个很好的自动
configuration for spring boot that
spring boot 的配置
allows me to configure an embedded in
允许我配置嵌入式
memory sort of active acute instance on
活跃的急性事件的记忆类型
the same node as my job application
与我的工作申请相同的节点
which means that for those of you
这意味着对于你们这些人
playing along at home you can just run
在家玩就可以跑步
this program you don't have to install a
该程序，您不必安装
JMS broker is this typical of what you
JMS经纪人就是您的典型代表
would do in a JMS of course not you'd
当然会在JMS中完成
use a proper standalone message broker
使用适当的独立消息代理
and this is typical of what you would do
这是你会做的典型
with the Apache come oh no I mean nobody
Apache来了哦，不，我的意思是没人
I don't think anybody is all that
我不认为任何人
impressed with JMS demos but what I want
对JMS演示印象深刻，但是我想要什么
you to understand is that this is a
您要了解的是，这是一个
messaging system it's some sort of
消息传递系统
middleware out there and it's one of
中间件，它是其中之一
more than 200 different offerings and
超过200种不同的产品和
offerings and options that you have in
您拥有的产品和选项
the camel ecosystem so if JMS isn't what
骆驼生态系统，所以如果JMS不是
you want maybe there's Kafka maybe
你想要也许有卡夫卡
there's rabbitmq maybe there's a s2
有rabbitmq也许有一个s2
maybe there's you know whatever there's
也许你知道那里有什么
just a proliferation of things out that
只是事情的扩散
you should be aware of okay so let's
你应该知道好吧，让我们
let's add some support that we want to
让我们添加一些我们想要的支持
use here so we're gonna add do I have
在这里使用，所以我们要添加我有
the actuator first of all I think want
首先，我想想要执行器
the actuator so spring boot starter
执行器，弹簧启动器
actuator spring boot starter I should
执行器弹簧启动启动器我应该
have added these back at the initializer
已将这些添加回初始值设定项
but I am i plumb forgot we want the
但我是铅垂忘了我们想要的
spring boot integration support we'll
Spring Boot集成支持，我们将
come back to that towards the very end
回到最后
all right already have it our door do
好吧，已经有我们的门了
you have that okay good so there's that
你有那个好的，所以有
and we've got the active active in
我们有活跃的活跃
qubits we want now the JMS support for
我们现在想要的JMS支持的qubit
apache camel if I'm not mistaking kind
如果我没有误会阿帕奇骆驼
of reviewing these here we've got org
在这里回顾这些我们有组织
pachi camel
帕奇骆驼
let's see or poor old camel is that not
让我们看看还是可怜的老骆驼不是
right yeah that is right
对对对
memories a little bad but you know I
记忆有点不好，但你知道我
think we'll get there this is the one
认为我们会到达那里，这是一个
drawback to not doing manual builds that
不做手动构建的缺点
often since I use a spring boot for most
通常是因为我大多数时候都使用 spring boot
of my work I don't remember how to do
我的工作我不记得该怎么做
this for a while so camel spring - boot
这一段时间了，所以骆驼的春天-引导
starter all right where we are look at
首先看看我们在看什么
that so there's this a spring wood
那就是春天的木头
starter
起动机
what we want is actually no we want the
我们想要的实际上不是我们想要的
camel Jamis starter right there's a
骆驼贾米斯首发吧，有一个
number of different starters and that's
数量不同的启动器，那就是
actually an another important to
实际上是另一个重要的
understand here there are 200 odd
明白这里有200个奇数
components or components in this case
组件或这种情况下的组件
refers to the camel nomenclature for
指的是骆驼术语
integrations basically you know things
整合基本上你就知道
that that camel can talk to and you can
那只骆驼可以说话，你可以
use camel without spring I know you're
没有春天就用骆驼我知道你是
terrified just as much as I am and in
和我一样恐惧
this odd hopefully increasingly rare
这种奇怪的希望越来越罕见
context there are just a few more
上下文中还有更多
options there are some more options that
选择还有更多选择
are available to you then there are for
可供您使用，然后有
those of you using camel with spring
那些在春天用骆驼的人
mood but these are things that don't
心情，但是这些不是
really make sense for a spring mood
春天的心情真的很有意义
application anyway things like OSGi
像OSGi这样的应用程序
right you're not gonna you're not gonna
对，你不会，你不会
use camel and spring mood and it was GI
用骆驼和春天的心情，这是胃肠道
together right that's a hopefully not as
在一起，那不是希望
calm in this situation right so there
在这种情况下保持冷静，所以在那里
are there's no support for that and
对此没有支持吗？
that's completely understandable but all
这是完全可以理解的，但是所有
the interesting stuff all the stuff you
有趣的东西，所有你的东西
probably want to talk to list in my my
可能想谈谈我的清单
humblest of opinions all the interesting
观点谦虚有趣
stuff that I would certainly want to
我当然想要的东西
talk to all that still works with
与所有仍然有效的对话
Springwood and actually it goes a step
Springwood，实际上迈出了一步
further you see there is the camel JMS
更进一步，您会发现有骆驼JMS
support and then there's a whole whole
支持，然后有一个整体
auto-generated auto configuration for
自动生成的自动配置
spring boot right and these this Auto
spring boot 权，这些自动
configuration is aware of of all the
配置了解所有
metadata related to these different
与这些不同相关的元数据
components so let's look at somethings
组件，让我们来看看
component to them so look look at what
他们的组成部分，所以看看什么
that means for spring boot users here we
这意味着对于 spring boot 用户，我们
have just some of the components right
拥有一些正确的组件
look at all these different components
看所有这些不同的组成部分
mqp support a PMA you know this is Apple
mqp支持PMA，您知道这是Apple
notifications atmosphere WebSockets atom
通知气氛WebSockets atom
Avro AWS number of different ats bits
Avro AWS不同ats位的数量
there validation the Box API brain entry
在那里验证Box API的大脑输入
API cache API I mean just so much stuff
API缓存API我的意思就是这么多
here right now cxf data set direct DNS
现在在这里cxf数据集直接DNS
disruptor those are EJB each cache
破坏者是EJB，每个缓存
elasticsearch at CD spring events if you
如果您在CD春季活动中使用elasticsearch
wanna publish an event into an
想要将事件发布到
application context what else we got
应用程序上下文我们还得到了什么
Facebook I mean files of course flat
Facebook，我的意思是文件当然平坦
pack I mean blink you know for tasks
包我的意思是眨眼，你知道任务
right there's the data processing FTP
右边是数据处理FTP
FTPS ganglia gee-off
FTPS神经节急救
for Google App Engine that kind of stuff
对于Google App Engine来说，
G login Google Calendar Google Mail Gora
G登录Google日历Google Mail Gora
geo Quarters oh my goodness look at that
地理宿舍哦，我的天哪
that's pretty cool hazel cast a spell or
榛树很漂亮，施了魔法
a CFS HTS to HipChat
从CFS HTS到HipChat
hl7 for healthcare right the healthcare
hl7 for Healthcare对医疗保健
world in fitness pan that's the Red Hat
健身锅里的世界就是红帽
database squid HTTP before I made this
我做这个之前的数据库鱿鱼HTTP
ignite this is a patch ignite it's
点燃这是一个补丁点燃它的
another data grid IMAP I'm a PEZ iron MQ
另一个数据网格IMAP我是PEZ铁MQ
Java spaces I'm not this is a this one
Java空间我不是这个
makes me sad I I'm a big Java space fan
我是Java的忠实粉丝，这让我感到难过
so Jake clouds J cache JDBC jetty J
所以杰克云J缓存JDBC码头J
groups JIRA
JIRA小组
JMS JM x JP a jolt JS c j SCH that's a
JMS JM x JP是一个震撼的JS cj SCH
SCP protocol the one you went used to
您曾经使用过的SCP协议
securely copy things I'm Michelle from
安全地复制我是米歇尔的东西
one UNIX node to another
一个UNIX节点到另一个
Castrol this is I think that's the
嘉实多这是我认为的
Twitter highly scalable message queue
Twitter高度可扩展的消息队列
from years ago
从几年前
you've got Cora you've got the LDAP
你有Cora你有LDAP
support LinkedIn
支持LinkedIn
logs leucine lumberjack metrics apache
日志亮氨酸伐木工人指标阿帕奇
mina that's the email server if memory
Mina是内存的电子邮件服务器
serves
供应
oh no sorry is that the meat is that the
哦，对不起，那肉是
what is that
那是什么
this is I think this is the thinking of
这是我的想法
something else
其他的东西
Mina is a what is Mina
米娜是什么是米娜
network application framework okay so
网络应用程序框架还可以
I'm thinking of a an email server that's
我正在考虑一个电子邮件服务器
built on top of me now that's out there
现在就建在我身上
that the Apache a produced which I
阿帕奇生产的我
recall bringing kind of good there's a
回想起带来的好处
you know mqtt support MSV mustache what
你知道mqtt支持MSV小胡子吗
else you got I mean my goodness it just
否则你会明白我的意思是
goes on Nagios I mean Neddie Neddie HTTP
在Nagios上，我的意思是Neddie Neddie HTTP
openshift
开班
paho comes bajo that same qtt support
paho来了bajo，同样qtt支持
PDF agent you know emissions post codes
您知道排放邮政编码的PDF代理
events email there's pop and pop three
事件电子邮件有流行音乐和流行音乐三
printers properties quartz jobs rabbim q
打印机属性石英作业rabbim q
r s 'let's res swagger are mi r NC relax
rs'让我们大摇大摆是NC放松先生
ng compact system route box RSS
ng紧凑型系统路由箱RSS
salesforce s AP netweaver schema tron
salesforce的AP netweaver模式
i'm not sure what the oh this is a
我不确定这是什么
pattern inside of inside of a camo so
迷彩内部的图案
you can do you can forward a call to
您可以，您可以将呼叫转接至
another endpoint in the same application
同一应用程序中的另一个端点
the same camel application s IP for
相同的骆驼应用程序的IP
voice right I mean s JMS a ground-up
语音对，我的意思是说JMS是一种基础
implementation of a JMS client batch
JMS客户端批处理的实现
support SMPP s secure right SNMP solar
支持SMPP的安全权SNMP太阳能
apache spark spark
apache spark spark火花
Splunk a spring batch spring innovation
Splunk Spring Batch春季创新
spring LDAP spring Redis spring Web
Spring LDAP Spring Redis Spring Web
Services sequel support stored procedure
服务续集支持存储过程
support SSH what else do I have my
支持SSH我还有什么我需要的
goodness Twitter undertow vertex virtual
善良Twitter突显了顶点虚拟
machines WebSockets XML security XMPP
机器WebSockets XML安全性XMPP
Yammer zookeeper oh my goodness I mean
Yammer zookeeper哦，天哪，我的意思是
there's just so many things that you can
有太多事情可以
use and there's even a number of them
使用，甚至有很多
that are out there but they're not part
在那里，但它们不属于
of the actual distribution that comes
实际分配的
with apache camel and this list is
与阿帕奇骆驼，此列表是
pretty impressive as well there's a lot
令人印象深刻的还有很多
of really cool stuff here so again you
这里真的很酷的东西，所以你再次
would be silly to ignore this wealth of
忽略这种财富是愚蠢的
integrations and if only because it's
集成，如果仅仅是因为
kind of nice to have one recipe to be
有一个食谱很不错
able to talk to all these things right
能够正确谈论所有这些事情
I'm sure you could write the code and
我确定您可以编写代码并
certainly there's integrations for all
当然，所有人都有整合
these things in the largest spring
这些东西在最大的春天
ecosystem but there's not a great
生态系统，但是没有一个伟大的
there's not a uniform interface for all
没有一个统一的界面
these things and so really a camel can
这些东西，所以真的骆驼可以
be that look at this this is a library
看看这是一个图书馆
for working with EDI parsing support
与EDI解析支持一起使用
using something called snoops which I've
使用我称之为“窥探”的东西
never even heard of but that's
从来没有听说过，但这是
interesting right lots of really
真的很有趣
interesting stuff out there so the point
有趣的东西在那里，所以重点
is all these components I have just
是我所有这些组件
mentioned
提到
where did I put that list Apache it was
我在哪里把那个列表放在Apache那里
called this one and I'm gonna call this
叫这个，我要叫这个
components here we are this list has you
组件在这里，我们是此列表中的您
know a lot of different components for
知道很多不同的组件
us to use and we can see those
我们使用，我们可以看到那些
components in our git repository here so
git存储库中的组件在这里，所以
github.com apache camel all right now
github.com apache camel now
camel has a large monolithic repository
骆驼有一个大型的整体仓库
and all that all the different bits are
所有不同的位都是
inside the components directory here and
在这里的components目录中
you can see just some of them alright
你可以看到其中一些
all these things here and that
所有这些东西
information all those different to
信息所有与
support all those different options
支持所有这些不同的选择
those different things that are
那些不同的东西
supported get into get turned into
支持进入
starters so starter and let's see there
初学者，所以初学者，让我们在那里看看
you go so you can see it says platforms
你去，所以你可以看到它说平台
spring boot component starter and here
spring boot 组件启动器和这里
are all the different auto-generated
是所有不同的自动生成的
again this is auto-generated a stone
再次，这是自动生成的石头
metadata that are encoded into the
编码为
different camel components for for Pecha
Pecha的不同骆驼组件
camel right this has been there for as
骆驼对，这一直在那里
long as Pecha camels been around for at
只要Pecha骆驼在附近
least for a long time to support
最少要长时间支持
metadata that tools need for auto
工具自动需要的元数据
completion and we'll actually see that
完成，我们实际上会看到
here we have in this in our in our
在这里，我们在这里
Springwood application in IntelliJ I'm
我在IntelliJ中的Springwood应用程序
running IntelliJ right now there's a
现在运行IntelliJ
plug-in that's loaded that supports
已加载的插件支持
apache camel parsing in a route syntax
apache骆驼解析路由语法
editing right inside the ID and so that
在ID内进行修改，这样
metadata is derived from metadata
元数据从元数据派生
encoded in these different components
编码在这些不同的组件中
that are available through apache camel
可通过阿帕奇骆驼获得
well there's a plugin that they use a
嗯，有一个插件，他们使用
build plugin that turns all that
构建插件，使一切
metadata into an auto configuration plus
元数据转换成自动配置
configuration properties that you can
您可以的配置属性
use to configure these different
用于配置这些不同的
components in the way that you might
您可能会使用的方式
anything else in the Springwood
斯普林伍德的其他一切
ecosystem and when you add these
生态系统，当您添加这些
dependencies to the classpath you get
您获得的类路径的依赖
the default configured component that
默认配置的组件
you want to use you don't have to
您想使用就不必
actually add it or configure it yourself
实际添加或自己配置
and that's just really cool i mean that
那真的很酷，我是说
is really really really cool so let's
真的真的很酷，所以让我们
let's take a look at that when we start
让我们开始看看
building an application using apache
使用apache构建应用程序
camel we create a route builder and so
骆驼我们创建一个路线构建器，所以
let's just say routes i'm gonna create a
假设我要创建一条路线
beam of type routes return
型式横梁返回
new routes builder and I'm gonna add
新路线生成器，我要添加
routes to the camel - context this is
骆驼的路线-上下文
one way to do it certainly that's to do
做到这一点的一种方法肯定是
that we can actually do that if we like
如果我们愿意，我们实际上可以做到这一点
I want to override the configure method
我想覆盖configure方法
though not this one so let's see
虽然不是这个，所以让我们来看看
uh-oh
哦哦
routes builder route to builder there's
路线建设者路线到建设者那里
a bit of a subtlety there and I'm gonna
那里有些微妙，我要
hit configure alright so there's that
点击配置好，这样
now when I'm in this API once I mean
现在，当我进入这个API时，我的意思是
it's just a spring mean right where
只是春天的意思
we're turning a spring mean already you
我们正在变春天意味着您已经
can see this is you're very much in a
可以看到这是你非常
spring boot world nothing is different
spring boot 世界没什么不同
about this once you're there you can
关于这个，一旦你在那里，你可以
configure very simple routes all right
配置非常简单的路由
so let's do that we're gonna say here
所以我们要做的就是在这里说
that we want to read from JMS and then
我们想从JMS阅读，然后
write that data to a file this would
将该数据写入文件，这将
just be the most that just or even
只是最公正甚至
better let's just do a simple file to
最好让我们做一个简单的文件
file so I'm gonna say from file and then
文件，所以我要从文件说，然后
I want to actually reference a property
我想实际引用一个属性
from the property sources in spring mood
来自房地产的春季心情
well camel automatically bridges that
好骆驼自动桥接
word mother I see that I can there
妈妈，我知道我可以在那里
that's from the intelligent support for
那是因为对
camel so if I click on this I can I hit
骆驼，所以如果我点击这个我可以打
control space and it's showing me that
控制空间，这告诉我
this is expecting a parameter so what
这是一个参数，所以
I'm doing is I'm using the component
我正在做的是我正在使用组件
each component has a you are n some of
每个组件都有一个
which some of those you are ends are you
你到底是哪个目标
are eyes but each component has a URM
是眼睛，但每个组件都有一个URM
syntax and it starts with the as you can
语法，它以开头
see here it starts with the name of the
看到这里它以名字开头
component and then you know this this
组件，那么你知道这个
URI you are in syntax tells you some of
您使用的URI可以告诉您一些
the supported options of which there are
支持的选项有
many you can see the things are optional
你可以看到很多东西是可选的
and things that need to be specified and
以及需要指定的内容
totem but they're named for so each
图腾，但它们的名字因此而得名
component has its own you are on and
组件拥有自己的位置，并且
normally if I wanted to configure my own
通常，如果我想配置自己的
you are in I would have to if I want to
如果我想你就在
configure my own application my own
配置自己的应用程序
component then I would have to do it
组件，那么我将不得不做
myself
我
so let's say I wanted to before we get
所以说我想在我们得到之前
into this actually before we get too far
实际上，在我们走得太远之前
down that line let's say I wanted to
沿着那条线，说我想
configure my own component right let's
配置我自己的组件，让我们
say I want to configure my own JMS
说我想配置自己的JMS
component right I would have to say
组件权我不得不说
private final camel context and I can
私人最终骆驼语境，我可以
just inject this this is the heart of
只是注入这个，这就是
the API in apache camel I'm going to
我要去的Apache骆驼API
inject it into the application and then
将其注入到应用程序中，然后
there I'll say this dot camel context
在那里我会说点骆驼语境
dot add component and here I can say my
点添加组件，在这里我可以说我的
JMS
JMS
Jamis component dot Jamis component and
Jamis组件点Jamis组件和
often you see it's taking a connection
通常您会看到连接
factor well we have the embedded
很好，我们有嵌入式
ActiveMQ support on the cross path so I
ActiveMQ对交叉路径的支持使我
can just say CFO and that'll give me a
可以说首席财务官，那会给我一个
auto configured you know spring will
自动配置，你知道春天会
Auto configure the activemq embedded
自动配置内嵌的activemq
apache activemq instance there and i can
apache activemq实例在那里，我可以
use that to configure my own custom
用它来配置我自己的自定义
thing but again if since we're using the
事情，但如果由于我们正在使用
starter and not just stock standard
入门者，而不仅仅是股票标准
spring boot I started a patch a camel we
spring boot ，我开始了一个骆驼我们
don't need to do that right that's
不需要做那个正确的
actually it been done for us in effect
实际上已经为我们完成了
and there's a default a name the default
有一个默认的名称默认
name in this case is JMS right so active
在这种情况下，名称是JMS如此有效
let's see JME yes there you go
让我们看看JME是的，你去了
is there an active in q1 ActiveMQ I
q1 ActiveMQ I是否有活动
think that's a slightly different we can
认为我们可以略有不同
use JMS is what we're gonna do so that's
使用JMS是我们要做的，那就是
that's actually the component that we
这实际上是我们的组成部分
use is the JMS component it back up
使用的是它备份的JMS组件
there so that's been configured for us
在那里，已经为我们配置了
and we can see that here we can see JMS
我们可以看到在这里我们可以看到JMS
component auto configuration whoops
组件自动配置
wrong one JMS component auto
一个错误的JMS组件自动
configuration from orga pachi camel
来自orga pachi骆驼的配置
component JMS spring boot and you can
组件JMS spring boot，您可以
see it's not it's not a two different
看到不是，不是两个不同
phone you would expect right there's
您期望有的电话
just a suit the code here is alright
只是一套西装，这里的代码还可以
look at that generated by the camel
看一下骆驼产生的
package maven plugin so all this is
打包maven插件，所以这就是
being generated automatically based on
根据以下内容自动生成
the metadata and there's validation
元数据和验证
that's happening here in the in the
这发生在
initialization and it's registering
初始化和注册
everything we need right it's that's
我们所需要的一切就是
really pretty amazing so this is all
真的很棒，这就是全部
there and the result is I don't have to
在那里，结果是我不必
worry about that and so we can reference
担心这个，所以我们可以参考
these files if I had if I had left this
这些文件（如果我离开的话）
code as is if I had left us there and I
就像我已经离开我们那里一样
wanted to reference a message coming off
想参考一条消息
of that Jamis cube right then I would
那个贾米斯立方体，然后我会
say from my JMS and the cue name would
说从我的JMS和提示名称会
be my cue right so that would be the
是我的提示，所以那将是
syntax I'd be an example syntax of a
我将作为一个示例语法
thing that produces messages okay
会产生讯息的东西
so let's remove this and we'll come back
所以让我们删除它，我们会回来
to in a minute now okay so from file
一分钟后就可以了
colon and then some sort of file system
冒号，然后是某种文件系统
reference so here I want to reference a
参考，所以在这里我想参考一个
property from the property source that
来自财产来源的财产
from a property source that spring boot
从 spring boot 的属性源
knows about so I'll say curly braket
知道所以我会说卷曲刹车
curly bracket that's the syntax for
大括号是它的语法
camel routes camel understands the
骆驼路线骆驼了解
syntax and but it has also bridged that
语法，但这也弥合了
syntax sentence that simple expression
简单的表达方式
language it's already bridged that with
语言已经与
the property sources in spring boot it
春季的财产来源引导它
knows about the properties in spring
了解春天的特性
boot whatever they are so if they're
引导他们无论是什么，如果他们是
coming from the the config server if
来自配置服务器，如果
they're coming from - - argument
他们来自--论点
application of properties whatever it
属性的应用
knows about the property source spi in
了解有关属性来源spi的信息
spring boot so I can just say user at
spring boot ，所以我只能说用户
home and that gives me the you know in
家，这给了我你所知道的
my case home day long
我的案件回家一天
whatever so then that'll be the user of
无论如何，那么它将成为
the home desktop and we're gonna say -
家用台式机，我们要说-
JMS all right
JMS没事
or better yet to another directory so
或更好的另一个目录
we're gonna do a very simple very simple
我们要做一个非常简单非常简单
rap just a very simple route there and
说唱只是一条非常简单的路线
I'm going to say file user dot home
我要说的是文件用户点回家
desktop well you know make this in and
桌面，您知道吗？
so be out all right so that's as simple
所以没事就这么简单
as it gets really I don't think you can
因为真的我不认为你可以
get much simpler than that and keep we
比这简单得多，并保持我们
don't need this for now well actually
实际上暂时不需要这个
give me this okay so let's see what that
给我这个好吧，让我们看看
looks like I'm gonna go ahead and run
看起来我要继续前进
this application and well-well run into
这个应用程序并顺利运行
our first problem with this code as it's
这个代码的第一个问题是
written as it's been written okay
写得很好
yeah we our first problem first of all
是的，我们首先是我们的第一个问题
properly with key Oh forgot this that
用钥匙正确哦忘记了这一点
wasn't the first problem I was
不是我的第一个问题
anticipating although it's nice that it
期待，虽然很好
was caught
被抓
okay there's our first problem the
好吧，这是我们的第一个问题
application is already shut down right
应用程序已经关闭了
so there's nothing keeping the main
所以没有什么可以保留主要
thread alive or it's I guess there's
线程还活着，或者我想那是
something keeping something alive but
保持生命的东西，但是
it's not apache camel pachi camel as far
远不是阿帕奇骆驼
as its concerned it doesn't get to stay
就其而言，它不会留下来
alive
活
and that's that's probably correct
那可能是正确的
because we know we haven't anything to
因为我们知道我们没什么要
explicitly prolong the thread so in
显式延长线程，以便
order for that to work we have to set up
为了使它正常工作，我们必须设置
a property here right this is the
这里的财产，这是
property that we can set thanks to
我们可以设置的属性
apache camel and that property is a
阿帕奇骆驼，那个财产是
let's see it's called spring but-- camel
让我们看看它叫做春天，但是-骆驼
dot spring but-- main one controller
点弹簧但-主控制器
equals true truly era so they go you can
等于真正的真实时代，所以他们可以走
see by the way do you see all those
顺便说一句，你看到所有那些
camel properties all of those come from
骆驼的财产全部来自
the different properties that are
不同的属性是
supported for these different components
支持这些不同的组件
right some of which on the classpath
对其中一些在类路径上
already but an infinite number of which
已经，但是其中有无数
are not on the class path so that's
不在课程路径上，所以
amazing we have all that support out of
令人惊讶的是我们拥有所有这些支持
the box now we can run this again you
现在我们可以再次运行该框了
can hopefully this time to the JMS
希望这次可以参加JMS
support won't trip down immediately all
支持不会立即崩溃
right looks like we're in business so
正确的看起来我们在做生意，所以
ignore the ActiveMQ stuff because i've
忽略ActiveMQ的东西，因为我
so we're not using it just yet but let's
所以我们现在还没有使用它，但是让我们
talk about this we've got now the
谈论这个，我们现在有了
application we've got the in and out
我们有进出的应用程序
directories if I go to my desktop I can
目录，如果我进入桌面，我可以
do I can delete in by the way let's
我可以删除的方式
delete in and start this again
删除并重新开始
there's in right so camel created it for
在右边，所以骆驼为它创建了
me so okay here we go echo random I'm
我好吧，这里我们随机回显
gonna use the random variable here I'll
我要在这里使用随机变量
say random dot txt echo hi to random txt
说随机点txt回声到随机txt
and now down here I'm gonna watch the
现在在这里，我要看
previous the output directory so I'll
之前的输出目录，所以我将
say watch - n 1 LS la alright talking
说手表-n 1 LS la好说话
every second I'm just gonna watch this
每秒钟我都会看这个
directory so if I do that again you can
目录，所以如果我再次这样做，您可以
see it's pretty quickly picking up the
看到它很快就会恢复
new files which is awesome so that's
很棒的新文件，所以
cool we've got this very very simple
很酷，我们非常简单
camel support there now we can do there
骆驼的支持现在我们可以在那里
are options for the file component right
是文件组件的选项
this is the producer of the data this is
这是数据的生产者，这是
the consumer we have options for that
消费者，我们对此有选择
component and if want to specify them
组件以及是否要指定它们
you can do that a couple of different
你可以做几个不同的事情
ways let's look at the simplest ones
让我们看看最简单的方法
that are in the you are in or the URL
您所在的位置或URL中的
syntax there right so file okay and the
语法正确，所以文件还可以，
options are typically found here all
通常在这里找到所有选项
right so I'm do want to auto create it I
对，所以我想自动创建它
can say auto pay equals false
可以说自动付款等于假
right so Auto create equals false and
正确，因此自动创建等于false并且
look at that if I hit control space the
看看如果我击中控制空间
IDE support gives me all these different
IDE支持给了我所有这些不同
options here the dunno file name could
此处的选项dunno文件名可以
be for example done alright that's the
例如做得好，那就是
file name that is gonna be created to to
将创建到的文件名
signal to some sort of consumer process
向某种消费者过程发出信号
that the file has been completely
该文件已经完全
written to the destination right so the
写到目的地的权利，所以
the consumer would know not to ingest to
消费者会知道不摄取
read or process the file that's just
读取或处理仅
been copied until it sees that done file
被复制直到看到完成的文件
right this is a very common pattern that
对，这是一个非常常见的模式
you'll see in messaging systems right
您会在邮件系统中看到正确的信息
you can say you can say that you want to
你可以说你可以说你想
provide a different file name you can
提供一个不同的文件名
say you know does it exist and it you
说你知道它存在并且它你
know what options do you have if it
知道你有什么选择
exists you can append fail ignore move
存在，您可以追加失败忽略移动
override right a lot of different
覆盖很多不同的权利
options there yeah so a lot of different
那里的选择是很多不同
a lot of different useful options here
这里有很多不同的有用选项
move existing keep that stride force
移动现有的力量
rights I mean all these different kinds
权利，我是说所有这些不同的种类
of things the bold ones
大胆的东西
are frequently used or recommended ones
经常使用或推荐的
these are the ones that you should pay
这些是你应该付的
attention to the other ones are less
对其他人的关注较少
interesting but they're useful right so
有趣，但是它们很有用，所以
all the support is there I'm showing you
所有的支持都在那里，我向您展示
the intelligent plugin but you're not
智能插件，但你不是
using IntelliJ that's just fine all of
使用IntelliJ就可以了
that stuff is just it's being generated
那东西就是它正在产生
directly from this same information the
直接从相同的信息
same source that generates this table
生成此表的相同来源
full of metadata is generating the spin
充满了元数据的旋转
boot starters and the configuration
启动启动器和配置
properties yeah so a lot of lot of
是的，所以很多
pretty interesting stuff here I'm you
非常有趣的东西，我是你
know truly impressed with that now it's
知道真正给它留下深刻印象的是
a pretty simple example alright let's
一个很简单的例子好吧，让我们
try something just a wee bit more
再尝试一点点
sophisticated okay
精致的好
just a wee bit so now let's look at JMS
只是一点点，所以现在让我们看一下JMS
all right
好吧
by the way our apps have route names
顺便说一下，我们的应用程序具有路线名称
before I get I move on to far so let's
在我开始之前，我要继续前进，所以让我们
say we're gonna give us a route ID this
说我们要给我们一个路线ID
is called a route so it's gonna be in
被称为一条路线，所以它将在
two out and then it becomes useful
两个出来，然后变得有用
because as you add more routes to a
因为当您添加更多路线到
system you would need to be able to
系统，您将需要能够
identify which is doing what and where
识别正在做什么和在哪里做
the errors are at dawn so right now you
错误即将来临，所以现在
can see when this application started up
可以看到该应用程序何时启动
it says a total of one route one of
它说一共有一条路线
which one are started you know and it's
您知道哪一个开始了
a route one well it's the generic name
一条路线很好，这是通用名称
that we got from that route but we can
从那条路线上得到的，但我们可以
give it an more human-friendly name a
给它起一个更人性化的名字
human recognizable name there so now
那里现在是人类可识别的名字
we're gonna say that we want to process
我们要说我们要处理
files and then transform the file into a
文件，然后将其转换为
string and then we'll send that on to
字符串，然后将其发送到
JMS ok so this is a slightly more
JMS好的，所以这要稍微多一点
involved example so here I'm going to
涉及的例子，所以在这里我要
say file user dot home just top two JMS
说文件用户点主页仅位于前两个JMS
all right and I'm gonna say route ID is
好的，我要说的是路线ID
gonna be and again this is completely
将会一次又一次完全
arbitrary you don't have to specify the
任意的，您不必指定
right idea but I'm gonna say file -
正确的主意，但我要说文件-
route ID or sorry file - JMS and here
路径ID或对不起文件-JMS和此处
I'm gonna send it to JMS and I'm gonna
我将其发送到JMS，然后
set it to the Q and the Q is the well
将其设置为Q，Q是正确的
it's a qo and it sent it to the Q in
这是一个Qo，并将其发送给Q in
this case is arbitrary I'm just gonna
这种情况是任意的，我只是
call it files it's just what I want or
称它为文件正是我想要的
whatever I want to call it in the
我想在其中称呼它
ActiveMQ broker all right now this is I
ActiveMQ经纪人现在可以了，这是我
think enough right here this would
想在这里足够
actually get you know this would work
真正让你知道这会工作
but we we couldn't really
但是我们真的不能
you know what do we get what do we get
你知道我们得到什么我们得到什么
that comes out of this component the the
从这个组件出来的
produced thing that comes out of that
生产出来的东西
doesn't necessarily belong inside of a
不一定属于一个
JMS broker so whatever actually want to
JMS代理，因此无论实际想要
do is I'm going to take the produced
我要做的就是拿走生产出来的
thing that comes out of this a file of
从这个文件出来的东西
some sort and adapt it you know one
某种适应它，你知道一个
transform it into something that I can
把它变成我可以的东西
then send to the downstream downstream
然后发送到下游下游
Jamis broker so what I'm going to do is
Jamis经纪人，所以我要做的是
I'm gonna say transform and when I
我要说的是转变，当我
transform it I want to specify which
转换它，我想指定
part to transform in this case I want to
我想在这种情况下进行转换的一部分
transform the body alright so I'm going
好好变换身体，我要走了
to say that the body that a body I'm
说那个身体我是一个身体
expecting is a type of generic file so
期望是一种通用文件，所以
I'm going to use a type token here
我将在这里使用类型令牌
direct file dot class and I'm going to
直接文件点类，我要去
write and create a little lambda here
在这里写并创建一个小lambda
I'm gonna use a nice functional API to
我将使用一个不错的功能性API
turn that gf into something that I can
把那个gf变成我可以的东西
then send back or send downstream right
然后向后发送或向右发送
so I'm gonna say try bufferedreader you
所以我要说尝试一下bufferedreader
know what I have here is I have a GF and
知道我在这里是我有一个GF，
the GF has a dot file and I can read the
GF有一个点文件，我可以阅读
file like this I can say file class dot
这样的文件我可以说文件类点
cast and turn that in so okay and I can
投下并转好，我可以
now um I want to turn this into a gf so
现在，我想把它变成gf，所以
let's see what is GF gf generic file
让我们看看什么是GF gf通用文件
yeah seems okay
是的，似乎还可以
yeah okay why are you not happy it file
是的，好的，为什么你不满意它
file F equal file actual file
文件F等于文件实际文件
get file ah right because I need to cast
得到文件啊对，因为我需要演员
this so file dodge class dot cast all
这个文件躲避类点全部
right well just took a powder here
好吧，只是在这里撒了粉
making things harder let's see maybe
让事情变得更艰难，让我们看看
didn't told you is having a bad moment
没告诉你你过得很不好
let's try return no for now just to ah
让我们尝试暂时不返回只是为了啊
there so it was something ready to some
在那里，有些东西已经准备好了
weirdness between IntelliJ and the
IntelliJ和
compiler no problem so we got that now
编译器没问题，所以我们现在知道了
we've got the actual file and we want to
我们有实际的文件，我们想
take the file and we want to unpack the
拿走文件，我们要解压
data in that file so I'm going to create
该文件中的数据，因此我将创建
a file input stream and I'm gonna wrap
文件输入流，我要包装
that in a an input stream reader and I'm
在输入流阅读器中，我是
gonna wrap that in a bufferedreader so
要将其包装在bufferedreader中，这样
I'm gonna do a lot of different things
我要做很多不同的事情
that need to be resource in I needed
需要成为我需要的资源
resources ation and then destruction so
资源化然后破坏
naturally this is a great use for the
自然，这对于
pattern the to try with closable pattern
尝试使用可关闭模式
in Java 7 so I'm gonna say
在Java 7中，我要说
bufferedreader in equals new buffered
等于新缓冲的bufferedreader
reader new input stream reader new file
阅读器新输入流阅读器新文件
input stream and I'm going to pass in
输入流，我要传递
the actual file and of course this
实际文件，当然这
creates a possible exception so I'll add
创建一个可能的异常，所以我将添加
a catch clause and we're gonna throw
一个catch子句，我们将抛出
this code I'm gonna throw this exception
这段代码我会抛出这个异常
if we should see it because there's
如果我们应该看到它，因为
nothing really that we can do here we're
我们真的无能为力
just kind of in the middle of the flow
只是在流程中间
and if we can't handle here then it just
如果我们在这里不能处理
can't be handled tonight so alright and
今晚无法处理，所以好
here we're going to say that we want to
在这里，我们要说，我们想
take the data so I'm gonna say return
获取数据，所以我要说返回
the buffered in dot read line or there
点读线或那里缓冲的
yet in dot lines I'm gonna take the
但以点线我要
lines which is a Java 8 stream of lines
lines是Java 8的代码流
I'm gonna collect them into a single
我要把它们收集到一个
string collectors dining I know that'll
字符串收集者用餐我知道那会
you know turn it into one string for me
你知道对我来说变成一串
okay
好的
there we go so I'm actually just taking
我们去了，所以我实际上只是在服用
the data that comes from the generic
来自通用的数据
file which is a camel wrapper around a
文件是一个骆驼包装
file to a generic type that has
文件转换为具有
information meta information about the
有关的信息元信息
file but it doesn't actually have to be
文件，但实际上并不一定要
a Java file that's kind of interesting
一个有趣的Java文件
it could be this is a generic file thing
这可能是通用文件
could be a wrapper around for example
例如可能是包装纸
something for an ftp server or something
用于ftp服务器的东西
else right
否则对
your your your agnostic of the
你你的不可知论者
underlying source good so there we go
基础资源很好，所以我们去了
now what do we want we want to see that
现在我们想要什么我们希望看到
that file that that information that
该文件，该信息
whatever it was in that file gets sent
无论该文件中的内容如何发送
to this Jain sq so finally down here
到这个Ja那教广场，所以终于到了这里
let's set up an example that just
让我们建立一个例子
listens to that queue for incoming
侦听该队列中的传入消息
notification so from JMS queue files and
通知，因此来自JMS队列文件和
all I want to do is a process the data
我要做的就是处理数据
right I'm gonna create a new processor
对，我要创建一个新处理器
here
这里
or better yet let's just write out to
或更好，但我们只写给
the file system that's a good idea
文件系统是个好主意
we can do that so just write it out to
我们可以这样做，所以只需将其写到
the file we'll say file to user dot home
我们会向用户点home发出的文件
desktop from JMS all right so we're
可以从JMS桌面下载，所以我们
doing a really circum look who this
做一个真正的外接看这是谁
route that goes from from a file system
来自文件系统的路由
to JMS to camel and then to the file
到JMS到骆驼，然后到文件
system again we're just taking the long
系统再次，我们只是花了很长时间
way around just to show that we can okay
只是为了表明我们可以
this I which is a little cute but hey
这个我有点可爱但是嘿
it's kind of interesting right alright
有点有趣吧
so and we want to call this route we
所以，我们想称这条路线为
should give it a name because we believe
应该给它起个名字，因为我们相信
in names names should be from so JMS two
名称中的名称应该来自于JMS两个
files
档案
how's that good ok now let's try it
好的怎么样，现在让我们尝试一下
let's go and restart the application
我们去重新启动应用程序
okay what did I do wrong connection
好吧，我做错了什么连接
factory must be specified right so
必须正确指定工厂，以便
that's this is a property that needs to
这是一个属性，需要
be specified in the JMS configuration
在JMS配置中指定
well Jamis configuration if you look at
如果您看一下Jamis的配置
this is actually a configuration of
这实际上是
properties right it can be it's a thing
属性可能是一回事
that gets specified by the configuration
由配置指定
properties so find usages and you can
属性，以便找到用法，您可以
see here that Jamis configuration
看到这里贾米斯配置
where's the Jamis auto country Jamis
Jamis汽车的国家在哪里Jamis
component auto configuration this is
组件自动配置，这是
from apache camel and here you can see
从阿帕奇骆驼那里，你可以看到
that it's got the Jamis component
它具有Jamis组件
configuration all right that's the thing
配置就可以了
that we want to inject that in turn is
我们想注入的是
aka you know it's been marked as a
也就是您知道它被标记为
configuration properties POJO so this is
配置属性POJO，所以这是
the thing that has all these different
具有所有这些不同的东西
properties that we want to use this has
我们要使用的属性有
been auto-generated based on the
是根据
metadata instead of a the apache camel
元数据而不是Apache骆驼
plugins we've got that here and we want
插件，我们已经在这里，我们想要
to be able to specify those properties
能够指定那些属性
and we could we could certainly try I
我们可以肯定可以尝试一下
mean we could say camel JMS of the
意思是我们可以说
component of DMF star connection factory
DMF星型连接工厂的组件
and then what well this is property and
然后这是财产有多好
it's expecting a pointer to a connection
它期待一个指向连接的指针
factory so that's not really a great fit
工厂，所以这不是一个很好的选择
for we're trying to do is it we don't
因为我们正在尝试做的是
want to use a property file to do that
想要使用属性文件来做到这一点
so instead we're going to use a
因此，我们将使用
component customizer okay so we're gonna
组件定制程序好吧，我们要
inject we're gonna tell it we're gonna
注入我们要告诉我们
give it a reference to this configured
给它这个配置的参考
connection factory just as we did before
连接工厂就像我们之前所做的那样
remember I said this doc camel context
记得我说过这个文档骆驼语境
god add component my JMS and I had to
上帝添加组件我的JMS，我不得不
give it a pointer to the connection
给它一个指向连接的指针
factory there right I'm not gonna you
那里的工厂我不会
know I need to do something like that
知道我需要做这样的事情
still but I need to affect the existing
仍然，但是我需要影响现有的
Springwood Auto configured JMS component
Springwood Auto配置的JMS组件
for petrikov as opposed to instantiating
Petrikov而不是实例化
and managing all that myself so and by
并如此管理自己的一切
the way most components will have a
大多数组件将具有
builder like that that's a it's not
那样的建造者不是
auto-generating that's just part of the
自动生成只是其中的一部分
API now in this case I need to use a
API现在在这种情况下，我需要使用
component customizer so I'm gonna say
组件定制器，所以我要说
static class
静态类
default JMS component customizer
默认的JMS组件定制器
implements component customizer for the
实现组件的定制程序
JMS component this is an interface a
JMS组件，这是一个接口
callback interface that when camels
骆驼回调接口
spring boot auto configuration perceives
Spring Boot自动配置感知
it it will call and give a chance to to
它会呼叫并给
override this particular component is
覆盖此特定组件是
the implantation of this particular
这个特殊的植入
component and it's typed by the type so
组件，并按类型键入
now we have the Jamis component there
现在我们有了Jamis组件
I'm going to say component dot set
我要说的是组件点集
connection factory and I want to give it
连接工厂，我想给它
a pointer to this connection factor the
指向该连接因子的指针
JMS connection factor that we got Auto
我们获得自动的JMS连接因子
configured for us by Springwood itself
由Springwood本身为我们配置
all right so with that done let's try
好的，这样完成后，让我们尝试
this again
再来一次
okay everything seems to be okay we're
好吧，一切似乎都好，我们
out you know we got the different routes
你知道我们有不同的路线
that started here total three routes
从这里开始的总共三条路线
okay and let's go down to the open
好吧，让我们开始公开
directory and we're gonna say to JMS
目录，我们要对JMS说
this is the directory that's gonna once
这是一次目录
I you know write data to this we'll see
我知道您会为此写入数据
it reflected hopefully here okay so go
希望它反映在这里好吧，所以去
there's from JMS and we can see that
来自JMS，我们可以看到
file 84 101
档案84101
alright so there's the text file that we
好了，所以我们有一个文本文件
just created and that's exactly what we
刚刚创建的，这正是我们
wanted to see right that's that's
想看对的就是那
actually gone through JMS the embedded
实际上通过嵌入式JMS
message queue and it's gone to the Janus
消息队列，它已经进入Janus
has been written out here which i think
我已经写在这里
is pretty remarkable now we have you
现在非常有我们了
know we've been content to leave the
知道我们已经满足于离开
name of the file up to its matching the
文件名，最多与其匹配
input file basically that's been
输入文件基本上已经
preserved in a header so when the
保留在标题中，因此当
message when the message arrives from
消息来自的消息
this file system there are some headers
这个文件系统有一些头
that are encoded in that message that
该消息中编码的
are perpetuated to JMS and that are
永久存在于JMS中，并且
visible to the consumer to the thing
消费者对事物可见
that's taking the main messages off of
这消除了主要信息
JMS and then writing it to the database
JMS，然后将其写入数据库
we can override some of that though we
尽管我们可以覆盖其中的一些
can process this data we can do all
可以处理这些数据，我们可以做的一切
sorts of interesting things so let's
有趣的事情，所以让我们
talk about some of that let's let's say
说说其中的一些，让我们说
suppose let's say I want to for example
假设我想例如
change a header or set a hitter well
更改标题或很好地设置击球手
there are some well-known headers that
有一些知名的标题
are expected for the camel filename
骆驼文件名
component right so here it's gonna ask
组件正确，所以这里要问
me another provided a expression like
我另一个提供了这样的表达
for example I can use a simple
例如我可以使用一个简单的
expression language expression here if I
如果我在这里表达语言
wanted to all right I could do body dot
我想可以做身体点
whatever lots of different things you
你有很多不同的东西
could do there and that's an expression
可以在那里做，这是一种表达
language that's unique to patch a camel
骆驼修补所特有的语言
but there is support for other kinds of
但也支持其他类型的
expression languages is there spell
表达语言有拼写吗
there might be spell there's a lot of
可能有咒语，有很多
difference right that's one option or we
差异权是一种选择，否则我们
can use a a supplier Java 8 supplier so
可以使用供应商Java 8供应商，以便
that's I'm going to do here I'm gonna
那就是我要在这里做的
say if you're asking me for a value I'll
说如果您要我的价值，我会
just say UUID dot random 2 string dot
只是说UUID点随机2个字符串点
dot txt all right so there's my updated
点txt没问题，所以我已经更新了
header now let's go ahead and we were in
标头现在让我们继续前进，我们进入了
this code and see if that gives us okay
这段代码，看看是否可以
so you can see the syntax for the old
这样您就可以看到旧的语法
number the old approach to JMS here's
编号JMS的旧方法是
this let's write this down oops
这让我们写下来
actually I want to say it from Jamis
其实我想跟贾米斯说
watch - n L SLA all right there we go so
看-n L SLA好吧，我们去了
you can see that the new file has a
您会看到新文件有一个
completely different name so here's one
完全不同的名称，所以这是一个
way of affecting the pipeline basically
基本影响管道的方式
as you can override well-known headers
因为您可以覆盖众所周知的标题
and those headers of course are also
这些标题当然也是
well documented so if you go down here
有据可查，所以如果你去这里
see all the different properties and
查看所有不同的属性和
here are some of the headers that you
这是您的一些标题
can you should expect to know about for
您可以期望了解一下吗
this different term for this for these
为此这些不同的术语
different components right and this is
不同的组件，这是
all allow this is automatically
全部允许这是自动的
generated based on the the component
根据组件生成
itself so this is not subject to to
本身，所以这不受
somebody being diligent I mean sorry
有人很勤奋我的意思是对不起
there's a lot of diligence I'm just
我只是很勤奋
saying this is not subject to somebody
说这不受某人的约束
updating the documentation every single
每更新一次文档
time there's a code change this just
时间有一个代码更改这只是
gets done automatically which is great
自动完成，这很棒
right now ah this is one way to change
现在啊，这是改变的一种方式
or customize the route here we've got a
或自定义路线，我们有一个
very simple route we're saying from this
我们从这里说的非常简单的路线
endpoint change the header and they've
端点改变标题，他们已经
sent it to this endpoint that's great
传送到这个端点很棒
here we're gonna say I want to take
在这里，我们要说我想吃
files from JMS route it transform it in
来自JMS的文件将其转换为
some way and then send it out now I
某种方式然后将其发送出去
could do a lot more there's a lot of
可以做得更多，还有很多
other patterns a lot of integration
其他模式很多整合
patterns beyond just transformations and
不仅仅是转换和
so on you can do a claim check you can
这样就可以进行索赔检查了
change the body you can delay it you can
改变身体，你可以延迟它，你可以
try a dynamic router using an expression
尝试使用表达式的动态路由器
you can do a enrichment you can actually
你可以做一个丰富的事情
say you know do aggregation and and
说你知道聚合和
splitting you can do an independent
分裂你可以做一个独立的
consumer consumer you can do a circuit
消费者消费者您可以做电路
breaker you can do a load bouncing you
断路器，你可以做一个弹跳你的负载
know do tracing add that to if you want
知道是否要添加跟踪
you can do all sorts of very interesting
你可以做各种各样非常有趣的事
things just by using some of these
只是通过使用其中一些
callback methods here right and the
正确的回调方法和
result is that you get the integration
结果是您获得了整合
flow that you want without giving up
您想要的流程而不会放弃
without giving up any flexibility here
在这里不放弃任何灵活性
so I encourage you to just peruse this
所以我鼓励你仔细阅读
later of course one of the most useful
稍后当然是最有用的之一
and methods here my name is useful
和方法，这里我的名字很有用
transformations is consumer that's re
转型就是消费者
process right so process gives you a
流程正确，因此流程为您提供了
number of different things that you can
您可以做的许多不同的事情
do with the data that's passing through
处理通过的数据
it so I can I can use post this body or
它，这样我就可以使用此身体
post this body and headers or post this
发布此正文和标题或发布此
body and give it a type you know
身体，给它一个你知道的类型
explicit type or process the exchange
显式类型或过程交换
and this is actually one of the more
这实际上是其中之一
interesting or poses the message so
有趣或带来信息
exchange is the it's the in and out it's
交流是进进出出
the thing that represents the bridge
代表桥梁的东西
between it's the door between two you
在两个人之间的门之间
know one component than the other okay
知道一个组件比另一个好
so I can actually process this exchange
所以我实际上可以处理这个交换
and I can you know I don't have to do
我可以知道我不必做
anything you could just say return
你只能说回来的话
exchange are we turn and then we can say
交换，我们转身，然后我们可以说
exchange dot get in write the message
交换点输入消息
the exchange has the the message that's
交易所的消息是
coming in you can do you reference that
进来你可以参考一下吗
here
这里
incoming okay and all I want to do now
传入的好，现在我要做的就是
is print out that data so I'll say in
打印出来的数据，所以我会说
dot get the body I suppose and we know
点得到我猜想的身体，我们知道
that this is going to be a string dot
这将是一个字符串点
class string so body will be this and
类字符串，所以主体将是这个
let's suppose I just wanted to print out
假设我只是想打印出来
what I see here so I'll get log get
我在这里看到的内容，以便获取日志
class well dot info body is what up okay
班级点信息正文是怎么回事
so I'm just gonna process the data but
所以我只是要处理数据
otherwise it's just going to pass right
否则，它将通过
through this code and go straight on to
通过这段代码，直接进入
the two files component right so try
两个文件组件正确，所以尝试
that again
再次
all right so now let's try this again
好的，现在让我们再试一次
and we can see that the body says hi all
我们可以看到身体向所有人说了声
right so we just we can insert ourselves
对，所以我们只是可以插入自己
in the process there and there's a lot
在这个过程中，有很多
of different paces where you can
不同的步调可以
exercise control in that process you can
在此过程中可以进行控制
you can you can consume the exchange
你可以消耗掉交换
itself the body if you want a typed body
本身就是身体，如果你想要一个有类型的身体
in this case you can say the body is of
在这种情况下，您可以说身体是
type string and I want to consume it as
键入字符串，我想将其用作
a string that would actually be easier
一个实际上会更容易的字符串
so here instead of doing all that
所以在这里而不是做所有的事情
unpacking as I did I could say a string
像我一样打开包装，我可以说一个字符串
and then just log factory dot get log
然后只记录工厂点获取日志
dot info the string body is string all
点信息字符串主体为字符串all
right so there's that other option and
对，所以还有其他选择
of course you need to start another
当然你需要重新开始
stands are there okay so we try that
站在那里，所以我们尝试
okay and the string body is high okay so
好的，琴弦的身体很高，所以
there's a another one and finally there
还有另一个，最后在那里
is the message the message objects the
是消息对象的消息
exchange I think is the most powerful
交流是我认为最强大的
you get access to everything there but
您可以访问那里的所有内容，但
you can use the message the message is
您可以使用该消息是
nice you say message and I can get
很高兴您说出讯息，我可以得到
access now to this I can get access to
现在访问此我可以访问
the body I can get access to certain
我可以接触到的身体
headers I can add headers I can add
我可以添加标题我可以添加标题
attachments you know you can do
您知道可以做的附件
interesting things you can set up a
您可以设置一个有趣的东西
whether there's an error or not you can
是否有错误可以
do also two interesting things here but
在这里也做两个有趣的事情，但是
I would you know I would stick with out
我想你会坚持下去
of the body or the exchange sometimes
身体或交换有时
you want you want to use a message
你想使用一条消息
either way you have full control which
无论哪种方式，您都可以完全控制
is really cool okay so we yeah we like
真的很酷，所以我们是的，我们喜欢
that now let's suppose one do something
现在让我们假设一个人做某事
conditional this is sort of an you know
有条件的，这是一个你知道的
point-to-point kind of thing there's no
点对点的东西没有
deviations in the route save of course
路线偏差当然可以
for some sort of exception handling but
用于某种异常处理，但是
you can also do a choice you can say
你也可以做出选择
okay when there is a route that I want
好的，当我有一条路线时
to match the win see new predicate when
匹配获胜时，请参见新谓词
the exchange matches a certain condition
交易所符合一定条件
right then we can do some interesting
然后我们可以做一些有趣的事情
things so we can say okay when it
事情，所以当我们可以说可以
matches this go to JMS queue errors
与此匹配到JMS队列错误
right so if math dot random greater than
对，所以如果数学点随机数大于
0.5 so we'll log this out boolean error
0.5，因此我们将注销此布尔错误
and log factory get log error
和日志工厂获取日志错误
era and of course you would set fault
时代，你当然会犯错
here you do you know you'd have a some
在这里你知道你会有一些
sort of fault to hand on the logic here
在这里提出逻辑有点错误
as well but you can say okay if you can
也可以，但是你可以说可以
inspect that exchange look at the
检查那个交流看看
headers look at the body determine where
标头查看正文，确定位置
that should go based on some condition
应该基于某种条件
here I'm using it for error handling I'm
在这里，我将其用于错误处理
saying send it to the errors endpoint
说发送给错误端点
and then end the choice and then
然后结束选择，然后
otherwise you know send it to JMS queue
否则，您知道将其发送到JMS队列
so a very simple example let's see one
一个非常简单的例子，让我们来看一个
error and this is Cobb viously this is a
错误，这是科布以前是一个
silly example right so let's let's see
愚蠢的例子对，让我们来看看
that actually no we can do something a
实际上，我们不能做点什么
little more interesting let's try that
稍微有趣一点，让我们尝试一下
oh say hello exchange dot get body gift
哦，打个招呼交换点送身体礼物
body string that class string hello and
主体字符串，该类字符串你好，
we can say bullion hello equals hello is
我们可以说金条你好等于你好是
hello dot contains hello there we go
你好点包含你好我们去
ant of it if it is hello then we say
蚂蚁，如果它是你好，那么我们说
that we want to return it to the hello
我们想把它还给你
queue otherwise we'll send it to the
排队，否则我们将其发送到
high Q okay or the everything else Q so
高Q好吧或其他所有Q如此
there we go
我们去
so let's try it so hello
所以我们来试试吧
and let's see if I got this syntax right
让我们看看我的语法是否正确
I do get this stuff wrong sometimes
有时候我确实弄错了
still otherwise to Jamis let's just say
还是跟贾米斯说，
files 10 right so JMS queue files okay
文件10正确，因此JMS队列文件可以
I think that's about right I think
我认为那是对的
that's right so right this again is
是的，没错，这又是
lambda and take extra care to take
lambda并格外小心
advantage of the IDS support for
IDS支持的优势
indenting remember this at formatter :
缩进格式器时请记住这一点：
off trick that I use them spring
春天我用它们的绝招
security it and it lends itself here as
安全它，它适合这里
well so tab tab okay good so when it's
好吧，Tab选项卡好吧，所以当它
this I think we can just sort this
这个我想我们可以整理一下
shortcut this a bit here
捷径这一点
everybody so when it's that go to hello
大家，所以当你打招呼时
otherwise that and then others end
否则那然后别人结束
alright so we're gonna get rid of that
好吧，我们将摆脱它
okay and formatter off or on rather we
好的，格式化或不格式化，而是我们
want to turn it back on so that
想要重新打开它，以便
everything else gets formatted correctly
其他所有内容都正确格式化
so good let's try that now
太好了，让我们现在尝试
we have no way of seeing I suppose
我们没有办法看到我想
we know that if it's if it gets sent to
我们知道如果它被发送到
hello there's nothing down stream to
你好，没有什么下游
process it so will will not see
处理它，所以不会看到
something arrived in the output
某些东西到达输出
directory I guess it's a is good enough
目录我想这已经足够了
testers anything okay so let's try that
测试人员一切正常，让我们尝试一下
working let's see if that works so PI
工作让我们看看是否可行
that gets delivered to the output
传递到输出
directory as we expect it to it let's
目录，正如我们期望的那样
just kill the files in here and there we
只是在这里和那里杀死文件
go so there's nothing in that directory
去吧，那个目录里什么都没有
let's try again there's that file
让我们再试一次
there's that one that one that one
那一那一那
okay so that that's working as we expect
好，这样就可以按我们期望的那样工作
now hello
现在你好
nothing right so we're not seeing it
没事，所以我们看不到
being river that's this because it's you
因为这是你而成为河
know the path is bifurcated it's going a
知道路径是岔路的
different direction which is what we
不同的方向，这就是我们
expect so you have flow control here you
期望如此，您就可以在这里进行流量控制
have the ability to dynamically
有能力动态
transform two routes do all the kind of
改造两条路线做各种
things you want to do with messaging in
您想要与之通信的事情
a messaging system now of course you
现在有一个消息传递系统
probably wouldn't have one route builder
可能不会有一个路线建设者
you could have a number of different
你可以有很多不同的
routes for example different application
路线，例如不同的应用
and you know all this time I've been
你知道我一直都在
very clear to very you know I've worked
很清楚你知道我已经工作了
hard to them to give these things route
他们很难给这些东西提供路线
IDs and the reason we would care about
ID和我们关心的原因
that is because we want to be able to
那是因为我们希望能够
see what the application is doing or
查看应用程序在做什么或
unable to to manage those routes so it's
无法管理这些路线，因此
rather to have a life cycle right those
宁愿拥有一个生命周期
loves routes are are interesting and so
爱的路线很有趣，所以
we want to observe them and ways we can
我们想观察它们以及我们可以采取的方式
support that of course with the actuator
当然可以用执行器来支持
so let's set up a few things that we
所以让我们设置一些
need for the actuator we're gonna say
对执行器的需求我们要说
management security enabled Eagles false
管理安全性已启用Eagles false
just for now you can set up spring
只是现在您可以设置弹簧
security if you like but in my case we
安全，如果您愿意，但就我而言，我们
don't need it so context path management
不需要它，因此上下文路径管理
context path equals actuator all right
上下文路径等于执行器
and I want to make the end points the
我想把终点
camel routes endpoints not we'd only
骆驼不仅会路由端点
rights I want them to be I want to be
权利，我希望他们成为我
able to post to them and to manipulate
能够发布给他们并进行操纵
them so this is the actuator support
他们，所以这是执行器的支持
here
这里
all right now when I run the application
现在，当我运行应用程序时
curl HTTP localhost:8080 forward slash
curl HTTP本地主机：8080正斜杠
actuator /r outs is it let's see what
执行器/ r输出是让我们看看
the actuator output is here yeah
执行器的输出在这里
actuator camel routes so camel routes
执行器骆驼路线，所以骆驼路线
okay so there's the output we can see we
好，所以我们可以看到输出
have different routes let's say I want
有不同的路线，假设我要
to stop one I want to just stop
停下来我只想停下来
processing into out this is not
处理成不是
necessary right now so I can actually
现在需要，所以我可以
post to this one here I'm gonna send an
发布到这里，我要发送一个
empty it should be post so curl - d2 the
空它应该张贴所以卷曲-d2
routes endpoint and look at this one you
路由端点，然后看一看你
can see that in and out has been stopped
可以看到进出已停止
right so was I was running before and
是的，所以我以前跑步了
then I stopped it that's a you know
然后我停止了那是你知道的
that's very convenient we can use the
这很方便，我们可以使用
actuator the Springwood actuator
执行器Springwood执行器
endpoints to to introspect and manage
进行内省和管理的端点
the routes themselves which i think is
我认为的路线本身
super convenient now we have looked so
超级方便，现在我们看起来很
far at some of the niceties that camel
远不及骆驼的一些精美之处
brings for the spring developer we've
为我们带来的Spring开发人员
looked at the nice DSL that it provides
看了它提供的漂亮的DSL
for building around definitions here it
在这里建立定义
is worth noting that there is for those
值得一提的是
of you who want to use that there's a
想要使用的人中有一个
XML DSL based on springs XML support
基于springs XML支持的XML DSL
that you can use in camel but I rather
可以用在骆驼上，但我宁愿
like this approach by the way I also
我也喜欢这种方法
inject the camel context here I injected
在这里注入骆驼上下文
it through the constructor because it's
通过构造函数，因为它是
just a regular beam and you can do that
只是普通的光束，你可以做到
but there's also an interface called
但是还有一个叫做
camel context aware right so you can
骆驼上下文感知正确，所以您可以
actually tell spring to in camel -
实际上告诉春天骆驼-
please inject a pointer to that camel
请给那个骆驼注入一个指针
context that's certainly one option and
上下文当然是一种选择，
we've looked at um you know ways to
我们看过了，你知道如何
customize the default behavior and how
自定义默认行为以及如何
that's working we looked at how the fact
这是有效的，我们研究了事实
we looked at the fact that you can
我们看着一个事实，你可以
actually custom register different
实际上自定义注册不同
components for example ones that aren't
组件，例如不是
automatically generated as part of them
作为它们的一部分自动生成
the spring boots starter you know plugin
你知道的 spring boot 入门插件
thing there that they have in the apache
他们那里的东西
camel project we looked at some of the
骆驼项目我们看了一些
observability support that's in there in
在其中的可观察性支持
out of the box now I want to talk to you
开箱即用，我想和你谈谈
about taking what we've got here and
关于拿走我们这里得到的东西
connecting it to spring and so we're
将其连接到春天，所以我们
gonna use spring integration because
将使用spring集成，因为
spring integration is just a simple it's
春季整合只是一个简单的
a nice API for integration as well but
一个很好的集成API，但是
but in particular the message channel
但特别是消息通道
which is what when you use it or when
何时使用或何时使用
you use a component in our apache camel
您在我们的Apache骆驼中使用组件
application that is specifically
具体的应用
designed to forward messages into a
旨在将邮件转发到
spring integration channel so for
弹簧集成通道
example if I want if I have a spring
如果我想要一个春天的例子
cloud stream and we didn't uh we did we
云流，我们不是，我们做到了
looked at a spring cloud stream in
看着春天的云流
earlier spring tips installment about a
较早的 spring 技巧 分期付款有关
year ago and that in that installment we
一年前，在那一期中
saw that a channel is a binding in
看到一个通道绑定在
spring code stream is just an interface
Spring代码流仅仅是一个接口
definition who's who's them bindings are
定义谁是谁，他们的绑定是
channel you know basically message
基本上您知道的频道讯息
channel space food parentheses
通道空间食物括号
parentheses semi-colon right it's just a
用括号括起来的分号对吧
interface method that has a channel
具有通道的接口方法
definition and that child definition
定义和那个子定义
gets turned into an actual connected
变成了真正的连接
hydrated connection to a broker be it
与经纪人的水合作用
RabbitMQ Pecha Kafka Google cloud
RabbitMQ Pecha Kafka Google云
pub/sub you know whatever it is whatever
pub / sub，你知道它是什么
binder you choose to use sprinkled
您选择使用的粘合剂
stream Kafka streams or you looked at
流卡夫卡流，或者你看着
that as well and a few in the recent
以及最近的一些
spring tips there's a lot of different
春天的提示有很多不同
bindings out there
绑定在那里
and you can use whatever you want you
您可以使用任何您想要的东西
want but the definition for the outbound
想要但出站的定义
connection to that broker is just an
与该经纪人的联系仅仅是
interface in our java code any
Java代码中的接口any
configuration lives in the property
配置位于属性中
files right so the connection to the
文件正确，因此与
Kafka topic is done in terms of
卡夫卡的话题是根据
configuration in the property files and
在属性文件中配置
that's related to the interface
与界面有关
definition in our java code so these
我们的Java代码中的定义
things are very convenient right you can
事情很方便就可以
actually mix and mix and mix these
实际混合并混合并混合这些
things together that's that's what we
在一起的事情就是我们
want to do here want to take advantage
想在这里想利用
for example of the rich ecosystem of
例如丰富的生态系统
Kafka a sort of a camel components and
Kafka是一种骆驼组件，
well then forward it on to a channel
然后将其转发到频道
which will then we can then do all sorts
然后我们可以做各种事情
of things with that channel could just
该渠道的事情可能只是
as easily be a channel that's
轻松成为
automatically created for us by spring
春季自动为我们创建
code stream
码流
could be a channel that gets fed into
可能是进入的渠道
spring dataflow it could be a channel
Spring数据流可能是一个通道
that's bound to be delivered who you
那一定会交付给你的
know whose payload whose contents are
知道谁的有效载荷的内容
bound to be delivered via Springs spring
势必通过Springs spring交付
NBC's especially in Florida springing
NBC特别是在佛罗里达州
meeseeks WebSocket support so all of
meeseeks WebSocket支持，因此所有
this stuff all these destinations are
这些东西都是这些目的地
reasonable for for apache camel users so
对于apache骆驼用户来说是合理的，所以
you can actually mix and match you can
你可以混合搭配
use camel to talk to these things for
用骆驼跟这些东西说话
which there may no may not be existing
可能不存在
spring support for example them I don't
春季支持，例如我不
know of a spring negation adapter that
知道弹簧取反适配器
does a s2 if you use camel to talk to
如果您使用骆驼交谈，则执行s2
that you can use camel to talk to
你可以用骆驼说话
whatever I mean there's a as we saw
无论我的意思是我们看到的
there's a very rich catalogue there and
那里有一个非常丰富的目录，
then you can forward those messages onto
然后您可以将这些消息转发到
a channel so let's do that it's got a
一个频道，让我们做一个
very simple spring integration flow here
这里的弹簧集成流程非常简单
and say integration flow and I suppose I
说整合流程，我想我
could use spring cloud stream but just
可以使用春天的云流，但是
to keep this as simple as possible oh
尽量保持简单哦
channel incoming turn and I'm just gonna
频道传入转弯，我将
create directly channel now channels in
现在直接创建频道
spring integration are named conduits
弹簧集成称为管道
through which messages flow and I want
通过消息流，我想要
to send a message that arrives let's say
发送一条到达的消息
that we send a message that arrives on
我们发送一条消息，到达
the let's create a route that takes the
让我们创建一条路线
data that comes off of the JMS hello
来自JMS hello的数据
queue and we'll send that into a spring
排队，我们将其发送到春天
immigration alright so let's do that
移民好吧，让我们这样做
so here well say from JMS queue hello to
所以在这里说的很好，从JMS队列向
spring integration and let's see what
春天整合，让我们看看
the component looks like for that spring
该组件看起来像那个春天
integration
积分
there we go yes just this just like that
在那里，我们就是这样
to say spring irrigation the channel
说春季灌溉渠道
will be called incoming there are some
将被称为传入有一些
options to want it to be in and out to
希望它进出的选项
want to be you know what is the output
想成为你知道什么是输出
channel that's that and is it sink rest
就是这样，它是水槽休息
that's true or false right so that's the
这是对还是错的权利，所以
base call we need to know actually
我们实际上需要知道的碱基对
that's it that's the whole thing I don't
这就是我不想要的全部
have to do any properties for that it
必须为此做任何属性
just works because it's running inside
可以正常运行，因为它正在内部运行
of a spring affright so when the
春天的事，所以当
messages arrive on hello hello q we had
消息到达你好你好我们有
no outlet for them before we would we
他们没有出路之前，我们会
would have expected to see them in the
本来希望看到他们在
files endpoint at some point but we got
文件终结点，但我们得到了
rid of that code so now if the message
删除该代码，所以现在如果消息
says hello it's gonna go to the hello
说你好，它将去你好
Jamis destination in our broker and then
在我们经纪人的贾米斯目的地，然后
our and then eventually it'll pop out of
我们的，然后最终它将弹出
the spring negation flow for this
春天的否定之流
channel so let's go ahead and do that
频道，让我们继续进行
now let's write the spring negation
现在让我们写春天的否定
processing code to process the messages
处理代码以处理消息
coming out of there and I'm only doing
从那里出来，我只是在做
this because I want we have to have the
这是因为我希望我们必须拥有
message the message has to get process
消息消息必须得到处理
we can't just you know buffer them and
我们不能只知道缓冲它们，
not do anything with them but we don't
不与他们做任何事情，但我们不
really need I'm using this formulation
真的需要我用这个配方
just because it's a simple example you
只是因为这是一个简单的例子
don't really need it in this case right
在这种情况下真的不需要它吧
we just want something to process that
我们只需要一些东西来处理
that that incoming message I'm gonna see
我会看到的传入消息
in flow configuration and
在流量配置中
all right so flow and we're going to say
好的，顺其自然，我们要说
return integration flows dot from this
从此返回积分流点
star incoming and all I want to do is
明星来了，我要做的就是
just you know print what we see so new
只要你知道打印我们看到的那么新
generic Handler and the data that we
通用处理程序和我们所需要的数据
expect is what we're gonna see a message
期望是我们将会看到一条消息
coming off of that queue we don't know
从队列中消失，我们不知道
what kind o so let's just go ahead and
那是什么样的，让我们继续吧
announce that we have the message the
宣布我们有消息
log factor don't get log kicked class
日志因子不获取日志踢类
print that out here and we'll say log
在这里打印出来，我们会说日志
got info new message that to string all
有信息新消息，将所有字符串
right so there's that not bad
对，所以那还不错
and we can put a breakpoint there build
我们可以在此处建立一个断点
the flow and we're done so that's the
流程，我们完成了，那就是
integration flow basically we're saying
整合流程我们基本上是在说
what a message comes in from a channel
频道收到什么消息
just pass it to the handler this is kind
只需将其传递给处理程序，这是一种
like the processor in camel and and then
像骆驼中的处理器，然后
a you know stop the flow stop the flow
一个你知道停止流动停止流动
if we had returned it I'm nominal value
如果我们退还了我的名义价值
then the flow would have continued but
然后流量会继续，但是
this case we returned a ain't no value
在这种情况下，我们返回的值没有
okay what did I do wrong there oh I
好吧，我在那里做错了什么
forgot to register the spring
忘了注册弹簧
integration starter so do I have that
集成启动器，我有吗
here nope I forgot to register camel
不，我忘了注册骆驼
spring integration starter or early
春季整合入门或早期
spring I'm sorry org apache camel
春天，对不起，org apache camel
looks alright alright good so there's
看起来还不错不错，所以有
that let's see what we have now we are
让我们看看我们现在所拥有的
expecting to echo um this output here so
希望在这里回显这个输出，所以
hello the new message is hello right so
你好，新消息是你好，所以
your message is hello so there we go my
您的留言打招呼，所以我们去了
friend with almost no code at all we
几乎没有代码的朋友，我们
have managed to a look at Apache camel
设法看了一下Apache骆驼
which is a rich framework with a lot of
这是一个丰富的框架，其中包含很多
integrations that we might might
我们可能会整合
leverage we should definitely feel to
我们绝对应该感受到
feel feel free to use it they certainly
随时随地使用它，他们当然
the the spring spring boot support for
春天的春天引导支持
pension camel is amazing right really
退休金骆驼真的很棒
well done very well done intubation
做得很好做得很好
there lots and lots of different options
有很多不同的选择
I'm sure that they didn't do all that
我确定他们没有做所有的事情
just so that we would ignore this wealth
只是我们将忽略这些财富
of options that are of course I'm sure a
当然可以肯定的选择
good number of spring users using apache
大量使用apache的spring用户
camel and maybe they didn't know about
骆驼，也许他们不知道
all this great spring blue to support
所有这伟大的春天蓝色支持
their so this video was just a meant to
他们，所以这个视频只是为了
just allude just to tease that some of
只是暗示着要逗弄一些
the amazing opportunities here for those
这些人的绝佳机会
of us who love integration in my
我们谁喜欢我的整合
background of course is messaging and
当然背景是消息传递和
integration I love messaging messaging
集成我喜欢消息传递
an innovation I worked on spring
我在春季进行的一项创新
integration quite a bit I love spring
整合颇多，我爱春天
integration I love camo I love anything
整合我爱迷彩我爱任何东西
that makes make it makes it easy to
这使得它很容易
connect otherwise disparate services and
连接其他完全不同的服务，以及
data now these are both lightweight
现在的数据都是轻量级的
intubation frameworks I love lightweight
我喜欢轻型插管框架
indication for interference these things
干扰这些东西的指示
hang off the side of your service and
挂在服务的一边
they provide an opportunity to all sorts
他们提供了各种机会
of interesting things now there's
有趣的事情现在有
actually preliminary support here in
实际上是这里的初步支持
Apache Campbell for spring cloud two
Apache Campbell面向春季云二
they do have some stuff that they're
他们确实有一些东西
brewing for integration with for example
酿造与例如
the discovery client abstraction there's
发现客户抽象
a there's a number a number of other
还有很多其他的
things that are going on here we didn't
这里发生的事情我们没有
get to talk about data formats we didn't
谈谈我们没有的数据格式
get to talk about all the different
谈论所有不同
kinds of components nothing come on
各种组件什么都没发生
today all the different kinds of them
今天所有不同的人
what are they called API is or SPI is
他们称为API或SPI的是什么
rather in apache camel we looked at
而是在阿帕奇骆驼中
components and and so on but there are
组件等等，但是有
other things that we could have looked
我们本来可以看的其他东西
at so we really only have only begun to
所以我们真的才刚刚开始
scratch a service i of course encourage
我当然会鼓励一项服务
you to to do so in leisure and with that
您可以休闲地这样做
my friends thank you so much for
我的朋友们非常感谢你
watching and we'll see you next time
看，下次见
you
您